Guide to the Centerbrook Architects and Planners Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Project records, Circa 1963-2004
  - "Marsh Estate", 1987-1991
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Box P100, Box P102, Box P116–P117)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box P136)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box P96–P98, Box P101, Box P103–P105, Box P107–P110, Box P113–P115, Box P118, Box P120–P126, Box P128–P129, Box P134–P135)
    - Mechanical/Electrical/HVAC Drawings (Box P98–P99, Box P105–P106, Box P130)
    - Photographs (Box P137, Box P157–P159)
    - Slides (Box P137)
  - May House, 1973-1978
    Job location: Old Saybrook, CT
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box M10)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box M10)
  - McElrath House, 1968
    Job location: Santa Cruz, CA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box N2)
    - Sketches (Box N2)
    - Photographs (Box N2)
  - McKee House, 1968-1972
    - Manuscript Materials (Box N3)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box B34)
    - Photographs (Box N3)
    - Slides (Box B32)
  - McKim House, 1988
    Job location: Fishers Island, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box M1, Box J33–J34)
    - Sketches (Box J31–J32)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box J30–J32)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box J1, Box J32–J33)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box J30)
    - Photographs (Box J1, Box J33)
    - Slides (Box J1, Box J33)
    - Negatives (Box J33)
  - McClintock Laboratory, Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory, 1993
    - Manuscript Materials (Box Q10–Q12)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box Q35)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box Q36)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box Q35, Box Q38)
    - Mechanical/Electrical/HVAC Drawings (Box Q37–Q38)
    - Photographs (Box Q11)
  - Middletown Inn and Renewal
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box B35–B36)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box B24)
    - Negatives (Box E76)
  - Middletown Public Elderly Housing, 1968
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box B37)
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Box F1)
    - Negatives (Box B38)
  - Miller, John House [House in the Berkshires], 1986
    Job location: Alford, MA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box M1)
    - Sketches (Box M3)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box M4)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box L16)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box M3)
    - Photographs (Box M1)
    - Slides (Box M1)
  - Miller, Peter House, 1979
    Job location: Burlington, VT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box D1–M1)
    - Sketches (Box D1)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box D8)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box D8)
    - Slides (Box D1)
  - Miller, Peter House addition, 1991
    - Sketches (Box E42)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box E42)
  - Minnesota History Center competition
    Job location: St. Paul, MN
    - Manuscript Materials (Box G11–G12)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box G47)
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Box G48)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box G1)
    - Mechanical/Electrical/HVAC Drawings (Box G48)
    - Photographs (Box G1, Box G12)
  - Monte Vista Apartments and Addition, 1965; 1973
    - Manuscript Materials (Box C3–K3)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box C46)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box C46)
    - Photographs (Box C3)
    - Slides (Box C3)
  - Moore House, 1966
    - Manuscript Materials (Box C2, Box A23)
  - Moore House, 1973
    Job location: Centerbrook, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box N4)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box N13)
    - Photographs (Box N4)
    - Slides (Box N4)
  - Murray House, 1969-1975
    Job location: Cambridge, MA
    - Sketches (Box C50)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box C50)
    - Photographs (Box C3)
    - Negatives (Box C3)
  - Naff House, 1968-1969
    Job location: Pajaro Dunes, CA
    - Photographs (Box M1)
  - NASA Project Tech House [aka Technology Utilization House], 1975
    - Manuscript Materials (Box K34)
    - Sketches (Box K33)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box K33)
    - Photographs (Box K34)
    - Slides (Box K34)
  - Nauticus (The National Maritime Center), 1988-1994
    Job location: Norfolk, VA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box S39–S58)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box S1–S24, Box S36)
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Box S25–S26, Box S35, Box S37)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box S38, Box S59)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box S31–S35, Box S37)
    - Mechanical/Electrical/HVAC Drawings (Box S27–S30, Box S35)
    - Photographs (Box S58)
    - Slides (Box S58)
    - Negatives (Box S58)
  - Nauticus II (the National Maritime Center), 1988-2000
    - Manuscript Materials (Box S61)
    - Sketches (Box S60)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box S59)
  - Navy Lodge Modular Housing
    Job location: Newport and New London, RI +CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box B32)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box B39)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box B40)
    - Negatives (Box B32)
  - Neurogen Corporation: administrative offices, 1988-1998
    Job location: Branford, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box M24, Box M47–M48)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box M20)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box M23)
    - Slides (Box M24)
  - Neurogen Corporation: Phase I, 1988-1998
    - Manuscript Materials (Box M24–M27)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box M16)
    - As-Built/Record Drawings (Box M20)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box M8)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box M15–M16)
    - Slides (Box M24)
  - Neurogen Corporation: Phase II, 1988-1998
    - Manuscript Materials (Box M24, Box M28–M31)
    - As-Built/Record Drawings (Box M20)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box M8)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box M17)
    - Slides (Box M24)
  - Neurogen Corporation: Phase III, 1988-1998
    - Manuscript Materials (Box M24, Box M32–M38)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box M18)
    - As-Built/Record Drawings (Box M20)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box M18–M19)
    - Mechanical/Electrical/HVAC Drawings (Box M19)
    - Slides (Box M24)
  - Neurogen Corporation: Phase IV, 1988-1998
    - Manuscript Materials (Box M24, Box M39–M46)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box M22)
    - As-Built/Record Drawings (Box M20)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box M21–M22)
    - Mechanical/Electrical/HVAC Drawings (Box M22)
    - Slides (Box M24)
  - New Haven College Student Housing
    - Sketches (Box B32)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box C20)
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Box C20)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box C20)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box B41)
    - Mechanical/Electrical/HVAC Drawings (Box C13)
  - New Haven Dance Center, 1969
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box B42)
  - No Bottom Development [Klotz], 1987-1989
    Job location: Westerly, RI
    - Manuscript Materials (Box P163)
    - Sketches (Box P161)
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Box P162)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box P160)
    - Slides (Box P163)
  - North House, 1975
    - Manuscript Materials (Box K4)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box K35)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box K35)
  - North Spec House, 1973
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box N14)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box N14)
  - Norwich Armory, 1977
    Job location: Norwich, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box J1–J2)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box J35)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box J1, Box J35)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box J36)
    - Photographs (Box J1–J2)
    - Slides (Box J1–J2)
    - Negatives (Box J1–J2)
  - Ocala House [Amrep Foundation], 1971-1972
    Job location: Orlando, FL
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box B43)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box M14, Box B43, Box E77)
  - Old Farm, 1973-1974
    Job location: Mt. Holly, Westhampton, NJ
    - Manuscript Materials (Box K4)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box K36)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box K12, Box K36)
    - Slides (Box K4)
    - Negatives (Box K12)
  - Orlando Housing [Amrep Foundation], 1972
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box I1)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box I1)
  - Orono Housing, 1971
    Job location: Orono, ME
    - Manuscript Materials (Box B32)
    - Sketches (Box C44)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box B44, Box B47)
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Box C44)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box M14, Box C44, Box B45–B46, Box E78)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box B44)
    - Negatives (Box B24, Box B32)
  - Otus House, 1963
    Job location: Berkeley, CA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box N2)
    - Photographs (Box N2)
    - Slides (Box N2)
  - Owen Brown Village, 1973-1974
    Job location: Columbia, MD
    - Manuscript Materials (Box C42)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box C42)
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Box C40, Box E79)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box I2, Box M14, Box C40–C41)
    - Slides (Box C3)
  - Parc de la Villette Competition, 1982
    - Manuscript Materials (Box E15)
    - Sketches (Box E43B–E43D)
    - Slides (Box E15)
  - Paumanack Manor Housing for the Elderly, 1973
    - Manuscript Materials (Box C2)
    - Sketches (Box C45)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box C45)
    - Negatives (Box C2)
  - Pearson House Addition, 1969
    - Manuscript Materials (Box E32)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box E43A)
    - Photographs (Box E32)
  - Percarpio House, 1979
    - Manuscript Materials (Box D4)
    - Sketches (Box D4, Box E80)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box D41, Box E80)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box E80)
    - Photographs (Box D4)
    - Slides (Box D4)
  - Peterson House, 1968-1973
    Job location: Tacoma, WA
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box B48)
  - Pfizer Plant Main Gate, 1994
    Job location: Groton, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box N18–N24)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box N15–N16)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box N25)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box N17)
    - Photographs (Box N18)
    - Slides (Box N18)
  - Pfizer Plant Master Plan, 1987-1998
    - Manuscript Materials (Box N18, Box N34–N39)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box N25, Box N43)
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Box N25, Box N43, Box N46)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box N1, Box N39, Box N48)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box N40–N42, Box N44–N45)
    - Mechanical/Electrical/HVAC Drawings (Box N46–N47)
  - Pfizer Plant South Gate, 1992
    - Manuscript Materials (Box N18, Box N28–N33)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box N27)
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Box N27)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box N1, Box N25)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box N26)
    - Slides (Box N18)
  - Piazza d'Italia, 1977-1978
    Job location: New Orleans, LA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box G13)
    - Presentation Drawings (Folder R48–R49)
    - Photographs (Box G13)
    - Slides (Box G13)
  - Pittsburgh Fountain, 1966
    Job location: Pittsburgh, PA
    - Sketches (Box N3)
    - Photographs (Box N3)
  - Place of Houses material [includes Charles Moore memorabilia], 1969-1975
    - Manuscript Materials (Box C2, Box N4, Box K5, Box G15, Box A23, Box B24)
    - Sketches (Box G1, Box D42, Box M49, Box F77)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box G1, Box D42, Box M49, Box F77)
  - Pond House, New England Island, 1992
    - Manuscript Materials (Box Q6–Q9)
    - Sketches (Box Q31)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box Q31–Q32)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box Q30, Box Q33)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box Q29, Box Q31, Box Q34)
    - Mechanical/Electrical/HVAC Drawings (Box Q29–Q30, Box Q34)
    - Photographs (Box Q9)
    - Slides (Box Q9)
  - Psychoanalytic Associates
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box B49)
    - Negatives (Box B32, Box E55)
  - Quanaduck Cove, 1973-1976
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box K37)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box K37)
  - Quinnipiac University: Carl Hansen Student Center (see also Student Union Renovation), 1991
    Job location: Hamden, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box L17–L21)
    - Sketches (Box L23–L27)
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Box L27)
    - As-Built/Record Drawings (Box L24)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box L24, Box L26, Box L34, Folder L29)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box L22, Box L24–L28)
    - Mechanical/Electrical/HVAC Drawings (Box L22)
    - Photographs (Box L17)
  - Quinnipiac University: Computer Center, 1983
    - Manuscript Materials (Box G15, Box E64)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box E73)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box E72)
    - Photographs (Box E64)
    - Slides (Box E64)
  - Quinnipiac University: Dining Hall and Servery Complex, 1986; 1988
    - Manuscript Materials (Box L17–L21)
    - Sketches (Box L32)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box L30–L31)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box L34)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box L30–L32)
    - Photographs (Box L17)
  - Quinnipiac University: Dormitory Complex, 1982
    - Manuscript Materials (Box G16–G23)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box G53)
    - As-Built/Record Drawings (Box G54–G56, Box G58)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box G51–G52, Box G57)
    - Mechanical/Electrical/HVAC Drawings (Box G56, Box G58)
    - Photographs (Box G23)
    - Slides (Box G23)
  - Quinnipiac University: Dormitory Village, 1991
    - Manuscript Materials (Box P175–P179)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box P167)
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Box P164–P165, Box P169–P170, Box P172–P173)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box P167)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box P165–P166, Box P168–P171, Box P173–P174)
    - Mechanical/Electrical/HVAC Drawings (Box P166, Box P170, Box P173)
    - Slides (Box P175)
  - Quinnipiac University: Echlin Health Sciences Center, 1982-1989
    - Manuscript Materials (Box N2)
    - Sketches (Box N2, Box N50–N51)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box N49)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box N51)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box N52–N53)
    - Mechanical/Electrical/HVAC Drawings (Box N52)
    - Slides (Box N2)
  - Quinnipiac University: Student Union Renovation, 1983
    - Manuscript Materials (Box L17–L21)
    - Sketches (Box L33)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box L34)
    - Photographs (Box L17)
  - Quinnipiac University: Suntraps, 1984
    - Manuscript Materials (Box G15, Box F28)
    - Sketches (Box F66)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box F30, Box F66–F67)
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Box F30)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box I3–I4)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box F68–F69)
    - Photographs (Box F28)
    - Slides (Box F28)
  - Raval Planning Study [Senior Citizens Housing Committee], 1971-1973
    - Presentation Drawings (Box I3)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box I4)
    - Photographs (Box I4)
  - Ray House, 1967-1968
    - Sketches (Box B50)
  - Reebok Corporate Campus, 1986-1988
    Job location: Stoughton, MA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box L35–L37)
    - Sketches (Box L38–L41)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box L38–L44)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box L16)
    - Photographs (Box L37)
    - Slides (Box L37)
  - Reid House I, 1987
    Job location: Cleveland Heights, OH
    - Manuscript Materials (Box M1, Box H19, Box P181)
    - Sketches (Box H19)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box H20–H21, Box H23–H25, Box H27–H30)
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Box H23–H25)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box H25)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box H22, Box H26, Box P180)
    - Photographs (Box H19)
    - Slides (Box H19)
  - Reid House II, 1988-1991
    Job location: West Falmouth, MA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box P181, Box P188)
    - Sketches (Box P183)
    - As-Built/Record Drawings (Box P187)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box P182)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box P182–P186)
    - Photographs (Box P181)
  - Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute, Folson Library Fountain, 1978
    Job location: Troy, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box D5)
    - Sketches (Box D5)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box D25)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box D25)
    - Photographs (Box D5)
    - Slides (Box D5)
  - Riley House I "Dunk House," Addition, 1976; 1986
    - Manuscript Materials (Box D4)
    - Sketches (Box D4)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box D29)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box E81)
    - Photographs (Box D4)
    - Slides (Box D4)
  - River-Dale Consumer Outlet and Travel Center, 1982
    Job location: West Springfield, MA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box G24–G28)
    - Sketches (Box G59, Box G66)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box G60–G66)
    - Photographs (Box G28)
    - Slides (Box G28)
  - Riverdesign Springfield, 1981
    - Manuscript Materials (Box E44–E48)
    - Sketches (Box E49)
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Box E49–E50)
    - Photographs (Box E47)
  - Roanoke "Design '79", 1979
    - Manuscript Materials (Box K8, Box I33)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box K8)
    - Slides (Box K8, Box I33)
    - Audiovisual Materials (Box I34–I39)
  - Roanoke Hotel and Convention Center, 1986
    - Manuscript Materials (Box K8)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box K7)
    - Slides (Box K8)
  - Roanoke Library Addition, 1983
    - Manuscript Materials (Box K8, Box K39)
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Box K10)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box K39)
    - Slides (Box K8)
  - Roanoke Market Building, 1985
    - Manuscript Materials (Box K38)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box K40)
    - Slides (Box K38)
  - Roanoke Parking Garages, 1986
    - Manuscript Materials (Box K8)
    - Sketches (Box K8)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box K8, Box K41)
    - Photographs (Box K8)
  - Roanoke Transportation Center, 1987
    - Manuscript Materials (Box K8)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box K42)
    - Slides (Box K8)
  - Rocky Neck Corporate Park, 1987-1988
    - Manuscript Materials (Box L37)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box L46, Box L48–L49)
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Box L48)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box L48)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box L45, Box L47)
  - Rosko Houses I and II, 1980
    Job location: Southampton, NY
    - Sketches (Box E51)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box E51)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box E51)
  - Ross-Lacy House, 1989
    Job location: Sherman, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box G29–G31)
    - Sketches (Box G68)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box I2)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box G1)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box G67, Box G69)
    - Photographs (Box G31)
    - Slides (Box G31)
  - Rottschafer House, 1980
    - Manuscript Materials (Box D4)
    - Sketches (Box D4, Box D37–D38)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box D35)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box D34)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box D36)
    - Mechanical/Electrical/HVAC Drawings (Box D34)
    - Photographs (Box D4)
    - Slides (Box D4)
  - Rowe House and Guest House, 1981-1982
    - Manuscript Materials (Box E52)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box E53)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box E54)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box E54)
    - Photographs (Box E52)
    - Slides (Box E52)
    - Sketches (Box E53)
  - Rubenstein House, 1978
    Job location: Maryland
    - Manuscript Materials (Box D2)
    - Sketches (Box D2, Box D39)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box D26)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box D27)
    - Photographs (Box D2)
    - Slides (Box D2)
  - Rudolph House I, 1970-1971
    Job location: Captiva Island, FL
    - Manuscript Materials (Box C2, Box B32)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box B51)
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Box B51)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box C47)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box B51, Box E82)
    - Mechanical/Electrical/HVAC Drawings (Box B51)
    - Photographs (Box C2, Box B32)
    - Slides (Box B32)
  - Rudolph House II, 1981
    Job location: Williamstown, MA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box E1, Box E55)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box E55, Box E71)
    - Photographs (Box E1, Box E55)
    - Slides (Box E1, Box E55)
  - Rush House, 1967
    - Manuscript Materials (Box N4)
    - Sketches (Box N4)
    - Photographs (Box N4)
  - Savin Rock Urban Renewal Project #2, 1966
    Job location: New Haven (West Haven), CT
    - Presentation Drawings (Box K36)
  - Saz House, 1969-1971
    Job location: Woods Hole, MA
    - Manuscript Materials (Box B53)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box B52)
    - Slides (Box B53)
  - Scheuer House and Landscape renovation, 1984-1988
    Job location: Larchmont, NY
    - Manuscript Materials (Box P193)
    - Sketches (Box P190–P191)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box P192)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box P189, Box P192)
  - Schaffer House
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box B54)
  - Schrader Development, 1969
    - Presentation Drawings (Box N1, Box N4)
  - Schub House, 1969
    Job location: Sag Harbor, NY
    - Presentation Drawings (Box B55)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box B55)
  - Sea Ranch Condominium #1, 1963-1965
    - Manuscript Materials (Box C2, Box B24)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box B56)
    - Photographs (Box C2)
    - Negatives (Box E55)
  - Sea Ranch Miscellaneous, 1963-1968
    - Manuscript Materials (Box B53)
    - Sketches (Box B57)
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Box B53, Box B57)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box B57)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box B57)
    - Photographs (Box B38, Box B53)
    - Slides (Box B53)
  - Sea Ranch Spec House, 1966-1968
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box B58)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box B58)
    - Photographs (Box B58)
  - Seattle Civic Center Fountain Competition, 1956
    Job location: Seattle, WA
    - Presentation Drawings (Box N1)
  - Shattuck House, 1980
    - Manuscript Materials (Box E38)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box E58)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box E56–E57)
    - Photographs (Box E38)
    - Slides (Box E38)
  - Sheeran Stores at South Street Seaport, 1983
    - Manuscript Materials (Box G32)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box G76–G78)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box G71)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box G70–G75)
    - Photographs (Box G32)
    - Slides (Box G32)
  - Shinefield House, 1969-1971
    - Manuscript Materials (Box K5, Box B60)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box B59)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box B61)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box B59)
    - Photographs (Box B60)
    - Negatives (Box B60)
  - Slater House, CA, 1964
    - Manuscript Materials (Box D3)
    - Sketches (Box D3)
    - Photographs (Box D3)
    - Slides (Box D3)
  - Slater House, CT, 1978; 1995
    Job location: Hamburg Cove, CT
    - Manuscript Materials (Box D3)
    - Sketches (Box D3)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box D22)
    - Landscape/Site Drawings (Box D22)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box D22)
    - Photographs (Box D3)
    - Slides (Box D3)
  - Solar Heated House - Experimental [aka Solar Spec House], 1970
    - Sketches (Box K46)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box K46)
  - Southern Illinois University, 1970
    Job location: Carbondale, IL
    - Manuscript Materials (Box B60)
    - Schematic/Design Development Drawings (Box B62, Box E83)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box B62)
  - Springfield Crafts Village, 1980
    - Manuscript Materials (Box E38)
    - Presentation Drawings (Box E59)
    - Architectural/Structural Drawings (Box E59)
    - Photographs (Box E38)
    - Slides (Box E38)